<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Jeff's Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://jawilson.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://jawilson.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-02-05T19:58:43-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://jawilson.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Jeff Wilson]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[On to the Next One]]></title>
    <link href="http://jawilson.github.io/blog/2014/02/05/on-to-the-next-one/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-05T19:35:23-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://jawilson.github.io/blog/2014/02/05/on-to-the-next-one</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Well I&rsquo;ve finally switched fully off my old VPS with <a href="https://www.linode.com/">linode</a>! There are
many reasons why I finally chose to do this, chief among them was cost. While at $20/mo it wasn&rsquo;t
exactly breaking the bank, I came to realize I wasn&rsquo;t really <strong>using</strong> it. No one really visited my
<a href="http://web.archive.org/web/20130930150100/http://blog.jeffalwilson.com/">blog</a> (much like they
won&rsquo;t visit this one), and its main purpose was to host my private Git repositories, serve as a
SOCKS proxy, and serve my mail.</p>

<h2>The Blog</h2>

<p>My old blog didn&rsquo;t get much traffic. Let me rephrase that, my old blog didn&rsquo;t get much traffic from
humans looking to read my blog. What it <em>did</em> get traffic from was crawlers, or even crackers,
looking to exploit my Wordpress installation. They even succeeded on multiple occassions. For a
random unheard of blog that no one cared about, it was simply too much work to keep up.</p>

<p>Once again I followed the path of my former peer from Virginia Tech
<a href="http://hokietux.net/blog/">Ben Hilburn</a>. Ben had switched to using
<a href="http://pages.github.com/">GitHub Pages</a> as a host, and <a href="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</a> as a
blogging platform. This worked beautifully for me. With this setup, the burden of hosting falls in
the both trusty and capable hands of GitHub, while I&rsquo;m free to post to my blog in a cozy, Linux
terminal addict friendly way, oh and don&rsquo;t forget everything is versioned with Git! This also means
that my blog is now just a set of static HTML/CSS/JS, very secure, and is still &ldquo;dynamic&rdquo; in that I
can easily update it with posts. The only issue was the manner of a comment section, which was
swiftly handled by the Octopress&rsquo;s built-in support for <a href="https://disqus.com/">Disqus</a>.</p>

<h2>Git Hosting and SOCKS Proxy</h2>

<p>TODO!</p>

<h2>Mailserver</h2>

<p>TODO!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[First!]]></title>
    <link href="http://jawilson.github.io/blog/2014/01/19/first/"/>
    <updated>2014-01-19T22:33:43-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://jawilson.github.io/blog/2014/01/19/first</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is a quick first post to my new <a href="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</a> blog hosted by
<a href="http://pages.github.com/">GitHub Pages</a>!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
